UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs 6000/016 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs
1944-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 169
6000/016 P
9.89 cubic feet
9.8 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection includes photographs from the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA), Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), and Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
5751536
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 27, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files 6000/016: UNITE Local 169 Files 6000/016 MB: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Memorabilia Banners 6200/001: UNITE HERE Local 169 Files
Textile workers -- Labor unions--New York (State)-- New York; Clothing workers-- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees -- Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 169. Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
5751536
- Demonstrations-Guess (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  6 photos
- Subject-Homework-Demo (Box 1, Folder 2)
  5 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Housing (Box 1, Folder 3)
  14 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-Contract Negotiations (Box 1, Folder 4)
  3 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-General (Box 1, Folder 5)
  90 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-General (Box 1, Folder 6)
  41 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-NYC (Box 1, Folder 7)
  9 photos
- Local 99 - Negatives (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-Greenwich, CT (Box 1, Folder 9)
  13 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-Morrow, Ga. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  11 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-NYC-Garment Rally (Box 1, Folder 11)
  27 photos
- Subject - SAKS (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-NYC-Wall St. Demo (Box 1, Folder 13)
  7 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-Leslie Fay-Pennsylvania (Box 1, Folder 14)
  8 photos
- Subject-Demonstrations-NYU Strike (Box 1, Folder 15)
  2 photos
- Strawbridge Demo (Box 1, Folder 16)
  16 photos
- Subject- Demonstrations-Tahari (anti-Chase) --6-21-2000 by Maria Stephen (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Subject-Demonstration-Warnaco (Box 1, Folder 18)
  1 photo, negative sheets
- Subject-Fashion (Box 1, Folder 19)
  27 photos, negative sheets
- Union Dept.-Education-ESL Graduation 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  4 photos
- Education-General (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Education-GIDC Classes (Box 1, Folder 22)
  23 photos
- Education-GIDC Events (Box 1, Folder 23)
  39 photos
- Education-Midwest School for Workers (Box 1, Folder 24)
  1 photo
- Education-Prenatal (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Education-Retiree classes (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Education-Skills-Retraining Class (Box 1, Folder 27)
  15 photos
- Education-Skills-Retraining Class-NYC (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Education-Shop Stewards (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Education-ESL-Color (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Education-EL-Anti-Discrimination (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Education-ESL-Black and White (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Education-Computer Exercise Class (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Union Dept.-Education-ESL Graduation (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Subject-Health and Safety-CPR Training (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Subject-Health and Safety-CTS (Box 1, Folder 36)
  25 photos
- Subject-Health and Safety-Deaf Members Workshops (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Environmental Hazards (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Subject-Health and Safety-General (Box 1, Folder 39)
  17 photos, 1 negative
- Subject-Health and Safety-General (Box 1, Folder 40)
  29 photos
- ILGWU Women (Box 1, Folder 41)
- ILGWU Women (Box 1, Folder 41)
  7 scanned photos
- ILGWU-Chorus (Box 1, Folder 42)
  42 photos
- ILGWU-Chorus (Box 1, Folder 42)
  negatives
- Labor Day 1988 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  4 photos, negatives
- Subject-Historical-Puerto Rico (Box 1, Folder 44)
  3 photos, [20] manuscript sheets
- Subject-Historical-Rivera Murals (Box 1, Folder 45)
  65 photo copied photos
- Subject-Historical 2000-ILG-100 year Anniversary. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  57 slides
- Subject-Historical - Unity House (Box 1, Folder 47)
  106 photos
- Subject-Historical - Unity House (Box 1, Folder 47)
  14 proof sheets
- Subject-Health and Safety-Health Care Crisis-Black and White [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 48)
  39 photos, 1 negative
- Subject-Health and Safety - Health Care Crisis-Black and White [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 49)
  15 photos, 2 cartoons, 1 negative
- Subject-Health and Safety - Health Care Crisis-Color (Box 1, Folder 50)
  45 photos, 3 negatives
- Subject-Health and Safety-Map Conferences (Box 1, Folder 51)
  21 photos
- Subject-Health and Safety-NJ Health Care Rally 5/1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Northeast Health Fair (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Rallies (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Social Security (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Train the Trainer (Box 1, Folder 56)
  22 photos
- 14th Biennial Convention for the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, May 1944, Chicago, Ill. [Panoramic photo] (Box 1OP, Folder 1)
- 23rd Biennial Convention for Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Atlantic City, May 14, 18, 1962 [Panoramic photo] (Box 1OP, Folder 2)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Union Health Center (Box 2, Folder 1)
  19 photos, 1 photo copy, negative sheet, 8 negatives
- Subject-Health and Safety-Union Health Center (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Subject-Health and Safety-Worker's Memorial Day (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Subject-Historical-Documents-ILG History (Box 2, Folder 4)
  manuscript sheets, newspapers
- Subject-Historical-1995-ACTWU/ILG Merger (Box 2, Folder 5)
  10 photos, negative sheet
- Subject-Historical-1950s (Box 2, Folder 6)
  2 photos, negative
- Subject-Historical-1950s/60s-Shop Photos (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Hurricane Relief (Box 2, Folder 8)
  51 photos, negatives
- Subject-Historical-1970s (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Subject-Historical-Education (Box 2, Folder 10)
  12 photos, newspaper articles
- Subject-Historical-ILGWU Housing (Box 2, Folder 11)
  newspaper articles
- Subject-Historical-ILGWU Housing-Co-Op City (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Subject-International-Brazil (Box 2, Folder 13)
  2 negatives
- Canada-T.J. Max-Alex Dagg- (Org. Winners), 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  6 photos & negatives
- International-Canada (Box 2, Folder 15)
  articles, newspaper articles
- International-Canada (Box 2, Folder 16)
  36 photos
- International-Canada-Labor Day, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  65 photos
- International-Canada-Labor Day (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Canada-Master Collective Agreement (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Montreal-Thermoplast-Gilles Dion, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Subject-International-China (Box 2, Folder 21)
  10 photos, 3 slides
- Subject-International -Ethiopia (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Subject-International Guatemala (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Subject-International-Haiti (Box 2, Folder 24)
  5 negatives
- Subject-International-Indonesia (Box 2, Folder 25)
  2 photos, 4 slides
- Subject-International-India (Box 2, Folder 26)
  8 photos, 1 slide
- Subject-International-Laos (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Subject-International-Madagascar (Box 2, Folder 28)
  1 slide
- Subject-International-Mexico (Box 2, Folder 29)
  18 photos, 4 negatives, 1 slide, 1 newspaper clipping
- Subject-International-Misc. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  79 photos, 2 negatives
- Subject-International-Morocco (Box 2, Folder 31)
  4 slides
- Subject-International-Nepal (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Subject-International-Paraguay (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Subject-International-Peru (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Subject-International-Singapore (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Subject-International-South Africa (Box 2, Folder 36)
  18 photos
- Subject-International-South Korea (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Subject-International-Thailand (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Personalities-Other Unions-ILG-Evy DuBrow (Box 2, Folder 39)
  24 photos
- Personalities-Unite Related-Susan Cowell (Box 2, Folder 40)
- UNITE-Pennsylvania (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Personalities-Unite Related-Edward Clark (Box 2, Folder 42)
  35 photos, 2 negatives
- Personalities-Bill Lee (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Personalities-Unite Related-Edgar Romney (Box 2, Folder 44)
  7 photos, 3 negatives, negative sheet
- Personalities-Other Bill Clinton (Box 2, Folder 45)
  28 photos
- Personalities-Other-Ralph Fasanella (Box 2, Folder 46)
  6 photos, 1 negative
- Personalities-Jesse Jackson (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Jay Mazur at Central States Meeting. (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Rally-Goya protest-3/2000--Philadelphia., Pa. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  17 photos, 1 proof sheet
- Rally-Goya-NYC 3/2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  22 photos, 1 proof sheet
- Rally-Chinatown 8-28-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Rally Local 590 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  26 photos
- Rally Workers - Center 6/18/1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  69 photos
- Rally Workers Center (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Retirees - "Retiring Right"- NYC -- 10/1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Union Dept. - Retirees - Seder slides (Box 3, Folder 8)
  10 negatives, 4 photos
- Retirees Support Teamsters - Senior Summer (Box 3, Folder 9)
  10 photos
- Retirees - GAP (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Retirees - Lafyette Chu, Brooklyn (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Retirees -- B/W (Box 3, Folder 12)
  38 photos, negative sheet, 3 negatives
- Union Dept. -- Retirees -- Acting Class (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Retirees Club (Box 3, Folder 14)
  63 photos, 2 negative sheets
- Retirees -- Color (Box 3, Folder 15)
  48 photos, 14 negatives, 18 slides
- Misc. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Loehman's Organizing Drive -- 3/1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Hurricane -- Dec. Unidad Local 99 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Crott Feture AP Automotive Systems - 3/1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  50 photos
- UNITE-Southern Regional Joint Board-Safeline Autoglass - 9/17/1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Finger Hut - 4/13/2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  31 photos, 1 proof sheet
- Vicki Schmeltzer - York, Pa. -- United Way Meeting. -- 11/11/1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Hurricane Relief - Honduras, Central America -- 1/19/1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Ralph Fasanella (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Kara Metz - Chinatown ILGWU and UNITE Meetings. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  45 photos, negatives
- UNITE faces, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  57 slides, negatives
- Robert Fox, Mike Moore, National. Linen - sol-Stetin-Arc Victory -- 2/2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  32 photos, 2 slides, negatives
- Seneca Knitting Co. - Seneca Falls, N.Y. -- Cara Metz (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Oscar de la Renta -- 3/1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Cara Metz - Belle Knitting -- Tai Chi -- GUESS (Box 3, Folder 30)
  36 photos, negatives
- Shops-Color-Worker-Portraits (Box 3, Folder 31)
  3 slides, 51 photos
- Child Labor-Photos, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  49 photos
- Shops-Color-Worker-Portraits (Box 3, Folder 33)
  negatives, 19 photos
- Shops-Levi (Box 3, Folder 34)
  proof sheet, 26 photos
- Shops-Malden Mills (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Shops-MGM Knitwear - Local 155 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Shops-Black and White-Worker Portraits (Box 3, Folder 37)
  11 negatives, 71 photos, 2 proof sheets
- Sweatshops-New Balance-Demo (Box 4, Folder 1)
  1 proof sheet, 9 photos
- Solidarity Day (Box 4, Folder 2)
  80 photos
- Sweatshops-Landscapes (Box 4, Folder 3)
  2 negatives, 12 photos
- Sweatshops-Child Labor (Box 4, Folder 4)
  2 photos, 5 negative sheets
- Sweatshops - BJ and B Factory - Dominican Republic - photos by Ken Leahy (Box 4, Folder 6)
  46 photos
- Sweatshops-"between a rock and a hard place" exhibit (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Sweatshop Rally -- 3/1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  35 photos, 1 proof sheet
- Sweatshops-Homework-Lower East Side (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Sweatshop Workers (Box 4, Folder 10)
  13 photos, 1 negative, 3 proof sheets
- Sweatshops-General (Box 4, Folder 11)
  32 photos, 1 negative, 3 proof sheets, 1 slide
- pg.1, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Subject-Trade-Fighting for our jobs (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Subject-Trade-FTA (Box 4, Folder 14)
  20 photos
- Subject-Trade-NAFTA (Box 4, Folder 15)
  37 photos
- Subject-Trade-Imports-Demos (Box 4, Folder 16)
  1 negative, 32 photos
- Subject-Trade-Imports-DC Rally (Box 4, Folder 17)
  41 photos, 1 negative
- Subject-Trade-Imports-LA Rally (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Uniform Campaign-NY Rally-City Hall-4/2001 -- Triangle Fire - 4/2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Uniforms - Local 23-25 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Jobs 14 Justice - Corporate Greed - Sofia Sazo (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Subject-Civil Rights-MLK Day 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- USAS - Founding Conference (Box 4, Folder 23)
  1 proof sheet, 15 photos
- Union Dept. - Union Label (Box 4, Folder 24)
  negatives, 6 photos
- Retirees (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Harpers weekly (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Triangle Fire Commemorations (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Subject-Historical-Triangle Fire-1998-Commemoration (Box 4, Folder 28)
  61 photos
- Triangle Fire - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  33 photos, 1 proof sheet
- Subject-Historical-Triangle Fire- 1997 Commemoration; 2000 Commemoration, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  46 photos, 1 proof sheet
- Triangle Fire -- 1991 Commemoration (Box 4, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO Convention -- October 1999 -- Los Angeles by Slobodon Dmitrov (Box 4, Folder 32)
  91 slides
- Historical-Performance (Box 4, Folder 33)
  12 photos, 1 negative
- Union Dept. - Political-Labor Law Reform (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Union Dept.-Political-Lobby Day--1998 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  8 proof sheets
- Union Dept.-Political Lobby Day on PNTR for China -- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  18 slides
- Union Depts. - Political - Lobbying (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Union Dept. - Political - New England Pol. Conference -- (Dartmouth, Mass.) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  negatives, 24 photos
- Union Dept. - Political - Phone Banking (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Union Dept.-Political - Pro-Choice (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Union Dept. - Political - Voter - Registration (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Strike - Leslie Fay (Box 4, Folder 42)
  72 photos
- Subject - Strikes - Sassco (Box 4, Folder 43)
  44 photos
- Strikes - General (Box 4, Folder 44)
  53 photos
- Sidney Hillman, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Solidarity Day (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Shops - Machinery/Materials (Box 4, Folder 47)
  18 photos, negatives
- Uniform Shops - Lion (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Education (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Sweatshop (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Education - ESL - Local 23-25 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Labor Day NYC - 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Labor Day, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Labor Day, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Labor Day, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  31 photos
- Labor Day, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Labor Day, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  35 photos
- Other Organizations - Asian, Pacific, American, Labor Alliance (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Made in New York (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Political - COPE School, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  negatives, 27 photos, proof sheets
- Labor Day - Albany, NY - April 2001 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Lobby Day - 2/4/2003 -- Schumer Meeting. - 2/5/2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  12 photos
- Political - Dukakis Rally, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  negative, 5 photos
- Political - Election 2000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  negatives, 19 photos, proof sheet
- Political, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Organizing - Costume Makers (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Organizing - Churchill Linen (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Organizing - Chusman (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Organizing - Dixie Kids (Box 5, Folder 22)
  6 photos, negatives
- Organizing - Domsey Fiber (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Organizing - Electrical So. (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Organizing - Ennis Automotive (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Organizing - Pscada (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Organizing - Fiber Dye (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Organizing - Fotajek (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Organizing - Florida Nursing Homes (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Organizing -- GUESS (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - A.J. Wright, Dist. Ctr. - (Fall River, Ma.) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  3 photos, negatives
- Organizing - Goodwill (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - LaMode (Box 5, Folder 33)
  2 photos, 2 negatives
- Organizing - Levis (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Organizing - Marshalls (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Mademoiselle (Box 5, Folder 36)
  19 photos
- Union Dept. -- Organizing -- Marvin Richards (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Union Dept. -- Organizing -- Midwest Sportsmen of Berlin (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Pa. Car Dealership (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Organizing -- Peerless (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Peerless - Atlanta (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Peerless - Boston (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Peerless - NYC (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Union Dept. -- Organizing -- Peerless - San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Pickets (Box 5, Folder 45)
  9 photos, 1 negative
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Plastonics (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Union Dept. -- Organizing - Proudstitga (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Organizing -- Fieldcrest (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Organizing - Richmark Curtains (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Organizing - Royal (Box 5, Folder 50)
  1photo
- Organizing - Serta - 5/1998 (Kristen Riggs) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  5 photos, 2 proof sheets
- Union Dept. - Organizing -- Simmons (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Soho Manufacturing (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Teximpor (Box 5, Folder 54)
  8 photos, negative
- Organizing - United Homecare Services (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Urtek (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Union Dept. - Organizing - Worker's Justice Center (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Organizing - York Bridge Plastics (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Organizing - YPS Sportswear (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Organizing - Black's Photo (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Organizing - Borden (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Organizing - Atrivm -- 1998 ---- Soccer League - 2001, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Organizing -- ILGWU -- General (Box 5, Folder 63)
  57 photos
- Organizing -- General (Box 5, Folder 64)
  35 photos, negatives
- Local 10 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Local 23-25 - (LRA) - 1997 -- Contract negotiations (Box 5, Folder 66)
- UNITE - Local 99 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- New England - Reg. Joint Board Mural - Winter 2001 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Southern Region (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Dallas (Box 5, Folder 70)
  20 photos, negatives, proof sheet
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 71)
  17 photos
- Shops - St. Louis Embroidery (Box 5, Folder 72)
  60 slides
- GAP, Albuquerque, N.M. -- Summer 2002 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  6 photos, 1 CD removed and placed in CD/DVD cabinet
- Shops -- Warehouses (Box 5, Folder 74)
- UNITE -- Organizing (Marshalls?) (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Shops -- Color (Box 5, Folder 76)
  32 photos
- UNITE -- Organizing - [Hillary Clinton] (Box 5, Folder 77)
  15 photos, negatives
- Hollander - Local 2420 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- UNITE - Guild (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Dynasty -, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Union Dept.-Contract Negotiations - Liz Claiborne (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Majestic Sportswear - Maria Rose Fashion, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Shops - Marshalls (Box 6, Folder 6)
  9 photos, proof sheet, negatives
- Windsor Trim - Findley, Ind. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Linen - Atlantic, Ga. and New Orleans, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Organizing - Kmart -- New Jersey (Box 6, Folder 9)
  8 photos, 2 slides
- Shops - Triple AAA in the USA (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Shops - Carlcraft (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Shops - Los Angeles (Box 6, Folder 12)
- UNITE - Portland, Me -- 10/2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  2 proof sheets, 1 CD removed and placed in CD/DVD cabinet
- Marshalls (Box 6, Folder 14)
  7 photos, 8 slides
- Shops -- Individualized Custom Shirt (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Ebonite Bowling Ball Factory -- Shops (Hopkinsville, KY) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  32 photos, negatives
- Wilson Football, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  17 photos, negatives
- Organizing -- National Linen (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Western Region -- Las Vegas -- 12/2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  3 photos, proof sheet
- UNITE/GAP -- Press Conference -- 5/16/2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Proof sheet, negatives
- Global -- Economy and Demo (Box 6, Folder 21)
  7 photos, negatives
- Subject -- Boycotts (Box 6, Folder 22)
- March on Washington, D.C. -- 30th Anniversary. (Box 6, Folder 23)
- MLK Day - Greensboro, NC -- 1/15/2001 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Jay Mazur (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Personalities - Other Unions -- AFL Leaders (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Personalities -- Other -- Dept. of Labor (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Personalities -- John Lewis (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Personalities -- Political -- Various (Box 6, Folder 29)
  43 photos
- Personalities -- UNITE Related -- Irwin Solomon (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Celebrities -- Organizing (Box 6, Folder 31)
  1 slide, 5 photos
- Chicago Laundries (3/1999); Veronica Mentonez, Arrow Shirt, Decatur, Ga. (Fall 1999) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  1 slide, 45 photos, 1 CD removed and placed in CD/DVD cabinet
- Subject - - Demonstration -- GAP (Box 6, Folder 33)
  14 photos, negatives
- GUESS -- Demo (Box 6, Folder 34)
  113 photos
- Subject -- Demonstrations (Box 6, Folder 35)
  95 photos
- Demonstrations -- Historical (Box 6, Folder 36)
  51 photos
- Subject -- Demonstrations -- Alfred Angelo (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Subject -- Demonstrations -- Anti-Sweatshop (Box 6, Folder 38)
  74 photos
- Daycare -- Fall River (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Daycare -- General/Political (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Daycare at Health and Safety (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Daycare Local 66-40 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Daycare -- Toronto (Box 6, Folder 43)
  33 photos
- ILG Video Library (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Knoxville -- Political/NAFTA (Box 7, Folder 2)
  3 proof sheets, negatives, 6 slides, 4 photos
- Charlotte, NC; Sarasota, Fla. -- Estimates (Box 7, Folder 3)
- SW Region, Cesar Chavez Rally, Immigration Rights, Dallas 3/31/2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Edgar Romney, Neil Kearney, Feliz Dia Mujer 3/18/2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  27 photos, negatives
- Rage against the machine (Box 7, Folder 6)
  newspaper and magazine articles w/photos
- ILGWU Convention (Box 7, Folder 7)
  proof sheets
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  127 photos
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  96 photos
- ILGWU Convention (Box 7, Folder 10)
  67 photos
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  100 photos
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  132 photos
- ILGWU Convention Newspaper (year of merger) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  newspapers
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  83 photos
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  93 photos
- AFL-CIO - 1999 Convention (Box 7, Folder 18)
  20 slides
- AFL-CIO - 1999 Convention (Box 7, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Convention -- 11/2001 --- Mike Short, Bruce Raynor (Box 7, Folder 20)
  83 photos, proof sheets